Stephen Popovich

WFR DEVELOPER



\bowtie	Email:
	stephenpopovich16@gmail.com

stephenpopovich	stephenmpopovich
Website:	

www.stephenmpopovich.com

San Jose, CA

SUMMARY

Web Developer with exceptional front-end development skills. Highly motivated to strengthen any organization. Strong leadership and communication skills with a mind for business backed by over four years of management experience. I'm pursuing a development opportunity where I can make a positive contribution towards success and growth.

EDUCATION

Web Development

March 2016

Coding Dojo, Silicon Valley Python, PHP and MEAN

Bachelor of Science, Business Management May 2013 San Jose State University, CA

EMPLOYMENT

Web Developer/Manager Morrocco Method Int'l

04/2017 - Present

San Luis Obispo, CA

- In charge of complete redesign, developement, monitoring and any adminstrative duties of website.
- Helped design Ads, UX, Labels, E-mail Blasts and Promotions
- Duties are SEO, mobile responsiveness, developement, debugging, and analytics of four seperate websites.
- Creatively enhanced the overall success of the business through managing social media, marketing, and contract efforts. *Also lead developer for gigongmastery.com, thehairshaman.com, www.morroccomethod.com/blog

Web Developer 06/2016 - 11/2016

Laplace Systems Inc.

Campbell, CA

- •Data mining, debugging, progress reporting, monitoring several sites daily, demoed prototypes and customer support.
- Back and front-end developer with an emphasis on creating front-end UI features.
- Creatively enhanced the overall success of the business through managing social media, marketing, and contract efforts.

Branch Manager 03/2013 - 10/2016

River City Build Supply Inc.

San Jose, CA

- Increased overall production and efficiency through managing a team of 16 employees in various roles including sales, dispatch, pruchasing, warehouse, and delivery.
- Practived leadership and contributed to a dynamic team through effective recruiting, hiring, training, and motivating of all staff members.
- Increased order through developing and implementing strong business controls and mainting the branch in an audit-ready status.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Front-End HTML/CSS **AngularJS** Photoshop **JQuery** Wordpress

Languages

Lariguages	
JavaScript	
Python	
PHP	

Databases

Other Technologies

NetSuite - MongoDB - Node.js - MailChimp Bronto - Microsoft Suite - Illustrator - MySQL

Projects

shop.MorroccoMethod.com (NetSuite, Javascript, HTML/CSS)

A luxury haircare e-commerce website backed by over 50 year's of business. A website that averages' 1.2 million visits a year from all over the world.

QiqongMastery.com (Wordpress, Javascript, HTML/CSS)

A new gigong e-commerce website, back by 40 years of experience. Full shop functional shop, introduction videos, relaxing gigong courses and much more.

Solar-link.net (Java, Spring, PHP)

Solar-link net a solar monitoring portal that gives the user information on their solar sites. Information such as enviromental benefits, energy usage, site status and weather.

FanFightTalk.com (HTML/CSS, Javascript)

A mixed martial arts news website. Articles, videos and pictures and a chatroom all surrounding the MMA world.